Tetris-Exercise 1- ReadMe

Names:
1) Shani Yunker, id: 204174858

2) Inbal Valdman, id: 308279231

Instructions for testing: 

Bomb:

1) The bomb can explode on any of the walls (left or right), by moving it to the wall.
In this case, if there weren't any blocks in the explosion range (3*3), the player won't lose any points.
2) In case the bomb deletes blocks and there are "floating blocks" in the board- they will stay floating (won't hard drop).
3) The minimal score is 0. There is no negative score.  

Moving the blocks:

1) move right: d
2) move left: a
3) hard drop: x
4) rotation (clockwise): w
5) stop joker: s

Rotation:

1) The rotation is prevented when there's a block or wall in the way of the current block,
meaning- anything that can cause the rotation of the block overlap a wall or a block will prevent the rotation.


 
General:

1) When the game is over, we display "GAME OVER" to the screen and delay for 4 seconds.
After that the player needs to click any key to exit the game (it doesn't return automatically to the main menu). 


